jantareview.com 2018-01-25

# JantaReview Privacy Policy | Local Search | Deals | Classifieds | Events | Forum and more

## Privacy Policy  

We recognize that privacy is important!. This privacy policy applies to your use of the JantaReview website, products and services but not does apply to any third party sites that may be linked to us. 

###  Information We Collect and How We Use It 

_Account information_ If you create an account to take advantage of the full range of services offered, we ask for and record personal information such as your name and email address.

_Public Profile._ Your profile information is kept private until you explicity agree to make your profile public. Then your profile is available on the community section of your city and locality page.

_Submissions._ We store and may publicly display your submissions in order to provide the services that we offer. When we display your submissions, we do so together with your account name (first name and last initial). The term "submissions" refers to the information that you submit or post to the our website for public display, such as business reviews, photos etc.

### Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [ click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

### Questions?

Questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to privacy[at]jantareview[dot]com.

###  Third party Trust Seals

* * *
